{
    "en-US": {
        "language": "English (US)",
        "language_select": "Select Language",
        "character1": "Character list 1",
        "character2": "Character list 2",
        "character3": "Character list 3",
        "tag_assist": "Tag assist",
        "original_character": "Original Character",
        "view_angle": "Angle",
        "view_camera": "Camera",
        "view_background": "Background",
        "view_style": "Style",
        "api_model_settings": "Model Settings",
        "api_model_sampler": "Sampler",
        "api_model_scheduler": "Scheduler",
        "api_model_file_select": "Model list",
        "vpred": "Vpred",
        "vpred_auto": "Auto",
        "vpred_on": "On",
        "vpred_off": "Off",
        "random_seed": "Seed",
        "cfg":"CFG",
        "step":"Steps",
        "cfg_hf":"HF CFG",
        "step_hf":"HF Steps",
        "width":"Width",
        "height":"Height",
        "batch":"Batch",
        "thumb_image": "Character Thumb Preview",
        "switch_gallery_mode": "Switching Gallery Mode...",
        "custom_prompt": "Custom Prompt (Header)",
        "api_prompt": "Positive Prompt (Tail)",
        "api_neg_prompt": "Negative Prompt",
        "batch_generate_rule": "AI rule for Batch generate: ",

        "regional_condition": "Regional Condition (ComfyUI)",
        "regional_swap": "Swap Character",
        "regional_custom_prompt": "Common Prompt (Both Side Header)",
        "regional_api_prompt": "Left Character (Left Tail)",        
        "regional_api_prompt_right": "Right Character (Right Tail)",
        "regional_character_left": "Character Left Side",
        "regional_character_right": "Character Right Side",
        "regional_origina_character_left": "Origina Character Left Side",
        "regional_origina_character_right": "Origina Character Right Side",
        "regional_overlap_ratio": "Regional Overlap Ratio",
        "regional_image_ratio": "Image Left/Right Ratio",
        "regional_str_left": "Left Conditioning Strength",
        "regional_str_right": "Right Conditioning Strength",
        "regional_option_left": "Left Area",
        "regional_option_right": "Right Area",
        "regional_error_not_comfyui": "Due to lack of API support, Regional Condition is only supported in ComfyUI.",

        "title_settings_save": "Save Settings",
        "title_settings_load": "Load Settings",
        "title_model_reload": "Reload Model/Lora/Settings List",
        "title_global_refresh": "Refresh Page",
        "title_swap_layout": "Right to left",
        "title_theme": "Toggle Theme",

        "api_image_landscape": "Landscape",
        "ai_prompt": "AI Prompt",
        "prompt_ban": "Prompt Ban List",
        "ai_interface": "AI Prompt Generator",
        "remote_ai_base_url": "Remote AI url",
        "remote_ai_model": "Remote AI model",
        "remote_ai_timeout": "Remote AI timeout",
        "ai_local_addr": "Local Llama.cpp server",
        "ai_local_temp": "Local AI Temperature",
        "ai_local_n_predict": "Local AI n_predict",
        "api_interface": "Image API Interface",
        "api_preview_refresh_time": "Generate preview interval (0=OFF)",
        "api_addr": "Image Interface IP Address:Port",
        "api_image": "Gallery",
        "gallery_thumb_span": "Thumb Preview",
        "output_prompt": "Prompt",
        "output_info": "Information",
        "ai_system_prompt_warning": "<h1><span style=\"color:orangered\">System prompt for AI prompt generator.<br>DO NOT MODIFY it if you DID NOT understand it!!!</span></h1>",
        "ai_system_prompt_text": "AI System Prompt",
        "ai_select_title":"Not use AI caption,AI caption once for multiple generation,Re-caption in each image,Use last AI caption result",
        "ai_select":"None,Once,Every,Last",
        "system_settings": "Settings",
        "image_info": "Image Info Reader",
        "image_info_to_generate": "Send image info to generator",
        "scroll_to_last": "Scroll to latest in Split Mode",
        "keep_gallery": "Keep Gallery",
        
        "model_path_comfyui": "ComfyUI model folder",
        "model_path_webui": "WebUI model folder",
        "model_filter": "Enable model name filter",
        "model_filter_keyword": "Model name filter keyword",
        "search_modelinsubfolder": "Search model subfolder",

        "api_hf_enable": "Hires Fix",
        "api_hf_scale": "Upscale by",
        "api_hf_denoise": "Denoising",
        "api_hf_upscaler_selected": "Upscaler",
        "api_hf_colortransfer": "Color Transfer",
        "api_hf_incorrect_upscaler": "Incorrect Upscaler selected, reset to default {}",
        "api_hf_random_seed":"HF Random Seed (ComfyUI)",
        "api_hf_steps":"HF Steps",
        
        "api_refiner_enable":"Refiner",
        "api_refiner_model":"Refiner Model",
        "api_refiner_ratio":"Ratio",
        "api_refiner_add_noise":"Refiner Add Noise(ComfyUI)",        
        
        "run_button": "Create Prompt",
        "run_random_button": "Batch (Random)",
        "run_same_button": "Batch (Last)",
        "run_skip_button": "Skip follow-up",
        "run_cancel_button": "Cancel current",
        "save_settings_button": "Save Settings",
        "load_settings_button": "Load Settings",
        
        "gr_error_creating_image":"[Error] Got error from Image API:\n[color=red]{0}[/color]\nCheck your [color=DodgerBlue]{1}[/color] console logs.",        
        "ai_system_prompt": "You are a Stable Diffusion prompt writer. Follow these guidelines to generate prompts:\n1.Prohibited keywords: Do not use any gender-related words such as \"man,\" \"woman,\" \"boy,\" \"girl,\" \"person,\" or similar terms.\n2.Format: Provide 8 to 16 keywords separated by commas, keeping the prompt concise.\n3.Content focus: Concentrate solely on visual elements of the image; avoid abstract concepts, art commentary, or descriptions of intent.\n4.Keyword categories: Ensure the prompt includes keywords from the following categories:\n    - Theme or style (e.g., cyberpunk, fantasy, wasteland)\n    - Location or scene (e.g., back alley, forest, street)\n    - Visual elements or atmosphere (e.g., neon lights, fog, ruined)\n    - Camera angle or composition (e.g., front view, side view, close-up)\n    - Action or expression (e.g., standing, jumping, smirk, calm)\n    - Environmental details (e.g., graffiti, trees)\n    - Time of day or lighting (e.g., sunny day, night, golden hour)\n    - Additional effects (e.g., depth of field, blurry background)\n5.Creativity and coherence: Select keywords that are diverse and creative, forming a vivid and coherent scene.\n6.User input: Incorporate the exact keywords from the user's query into the prompt where appropriate.\n7.Emphasis handling: If the user emphasizes a particular aspect, you may increase the number of keywords in that category (up to 6), but ensure the total number of keywords remains between 8 and 16.\n8.Character description: You may describe actions and expressions but must not mention specific character traits (such as gender or age). Words that imply a character (e.g., \"warrior\") are allowed as long as they do not violate the prohibited keywords.\n9.Output: Provide the answer as a single line of comma-separated keywords in English, do not include any responses other than keywords.\n10. Output Example:nature style, eating, forest, meadow, sunlight, vibrant colors, close-up, detailed, serene, peaceful, green foliage, wild berries, natural textures, soft focus, shallow depth of field, tranquil atmosphere\nPrompt for the following theme:",
        
        "overlay_title": "Now generating...",
        "overlay_te": "Elapsed time:",
        "overlay_sec": "seconds",

        "generate_ai": "Wait for AI promot ...",
        "generate_start": "Now generating {0}/{1}...",
        
        "lora_info": "LoRA info",
        "lora_trigger_words": "Trigger Words (Top 10): ",
        "lora_metadata": "Metadata:",
        "lora_no_metadata": "File read error or metadata was intentionally removed",
        "lora_model_strength": "Model strength",
        "lora_clip_strength": "CLIP strength",
        "lora_enable_title": "Method:ALL,Base,HiFix,OFF",

        "right_menu_copy_image": "Copy Image",
        "right_menu_copy_image_metadata": "Copy Metadata",
        "right_menu_clear_gallery": "Clear Gallery",
        "right_menu_test_ai_generate": "Test AI Generate",
        "right_menu_send_lora_to_slot": "Send LoRA to Slot",

        "save_settings_title": "Save Settings file\nPlease enter the name of the file to be saved.",
        "save_settings_success": "{0} Saved!",
        "save_settings_failed": "Save {0} failed!",
        
        "setup_yes": "Yes",
        "setup_no": "No",
        "setup_ok": "Okay",
        "setup_cancel": "Cancel",
        "setup_greet_message": "Hello, the setup wizard will start automatically the first time the program is started or if the settings.json file is not found, please follow the instructions to complete the initialisation settings.",
        "setup_webui_comfyui_select": "Please select the backend type you will be using.",
        "setup_model_folder": "Please enter the directory where your model files (safetensors) are located. It is recommended to copy the path from address bar.",
        "setup_webui_comfyui_api_addr": "Please enter the address for {0} backend. You can copy the IP address and port from your browser.",
        "setup_model_filter": "Please select whether or not to enable the model name filters.",
        "setup_model_filter_keyword": "Please set the whitelist filters keywords.\nIf multiple keywords are needed, separate them with commas (,).",
        "setup_search_modelinsubfolder": "Search for model files in subfolders of the model folder.",

        "setup_remote_ai_interface": "Configure the AI language model interface (None to disable, Remote for remote, Local for local).",
        "setup_remote_ai_addr": "Please enter the API address for the remote language model.",
        "setup_remote_ai_model": "Please enter the name of the remote language model.",
        "setup_remote_ai_api_key": "Please enter your API key for the remote language model.",
        "setup_local_ai_addr": "Please enter the API address for your local language model.",

        "setup_done": "Initial setup is complete, and the configuration has been saved as settings.json.\nIf you are using ComfyUI, please enable Dev Mode in the settings.\nIf you are using WebUI, modify webui-user.bat and add COMMANDLINE_ARGS= --api.",  
        "setup_skip_wizard": "Skip following setup?"
    },
    "zh-CN": {
        "language": "中文（简体）",
        "language_select": "界面语言",
        "character1": "角色1",
        "character2": "角色2",
        "character3": "角色3",
        "tag_assist": "角色标签辅助",
        "original_character": "自定义及原创角色",
        "view_angle": "视角",
        "view_camera": "镜头",
        "view_background": "背景",
        "view_style": "风格",
        "api_model_settings": "模型设置",
        "api_model_sampler": "采样器",
        "api_model_scheduler": "调度器",
        "api_model_file_select": "模型选择",
        "vpred": "V预测模型",
        "vpred_auto": "自动",
        "vpred_on": "启动",
        "vpred_off": "关闭",
        "random_seed": "种子",
        "cfg":"引导",
        "step":"步数",
        "cfg_hf":"高修引导",
        "step_hf":"高修步数",
        "width":"宽度",
        "height":"高度",
        "batch":"批量",
        "thumb_image": "角色预览",
        "switch_gallery_mode": "正在切换显示模式……",
        "custom_prompt": "自定义提示词（放在最前）",
        "api_prompt": "效果提示词（放在末尾）",        
        "api_neg_prompt": "负面提示词",
        "batch_generate_rule": "AI填词规则：",

        "regional_condition": "双人分区采样（ComfyUI）",
        "regional_swap": "交换角色位置",
        "regional_custom_prompt": "通用提示词（两侧最前）",
        "regional_api_prompt": "左侧角色提示词（左侧末尾）",        
        "regional_api_prompt_right": "右侧角色提示词（右侧末尾）",
        "regional_character_left": "分区左侧角色",
        "regional_character_right": "分区右侧角色",
        "regional_origina_character_left": "分区左侧原创角色",
        "regional_origina_character_right": "分区右侧原创角色",
        "regional_overlap_ratio": "分区相互覆盖比例",
        "regional_image_ratio": "左右分区比例",
        "regional_str_left": "左采样强度",
        "regional_str_right": "右采样强度",
        "regional_option_left": "左采样区域",
        "regional_option_right": "右采样区域",
        "regional_error_not_comfyui": "注意，由于缺少API支持，当前分区采样仅支持ComfyUI。",

        "title_settings_save": "保存设置",
        "title_settings_load": "读取设置",
        "title_model_reload": "重新载入（模型、LoRA、设置）列表",
        "title_global_refresh": "刷新页面",
        "title_swap_layout": "切换左右",
        "title_theme": "切换主题",

        "api_image_landscape": "宽高互换",
        "ai_prompt": "AI提示词（用于生成填词）",
        "prompt_ban": "提示词黑名单",
        "ai_interface": "AI填词设置",
        "remote_ai_base_url": "远程AI地址",
        "remote_ai_model": "远程AI模型",
        "remote_ai_timeout": "远程AI超时（秒）",
        "ai_local_addr": "本地 Llama.cpp 服务地址",
        "ai_local_temp": "本地AI温度（Temperature）",
        "ai_local_n_predict": "本地AI回复长度（n_predict）",
        "api_interface": "接口API选择",
        "api_preview_refresh_time": "预览图刷新间隔（0为关闭预览）",
        "api_addr": "接口API地址（IP Address:Port）",
        "api_image": "输出",
        "gallery_thumb_span": "角色预览",
        "output_prompt": "最终提示词",
        "output_info": "相关信息",
        "ai_system_prompt_warning": "<h1><span style=\"color:orangered\">AI系统提示词，建议使用英文<br>如果你不清楚这是干什么的，不要修改！！！</span></h1>",
        "ai_system_prompt_text": "AI系统提示词",
        "ai_select_title":"不使用AI题词,多次生成时只运行一次AI题词,每张图片都用AI重新题词,使用上次的AI题词结果",
        "ai_select":"关闭,单次,每次,上次",
        "system_settings": "设置",
        "image_info": "读取图片信息",
        "image_info_to_generate": "传输图片数据到生成器",
        "scroll_to_last": "分割模式自动选择最新",
        "keep_gallery": "保留图库",
        
        "model_path_comfyui": "ComfyUI模型路径",
        "model_path_webui": "WebUI模型路径",
        "model_filter": "启用模型名称过滤",
        "model_filter_keyword": "模型名称过滤规则",
        "search_modelinsubfolder": "搜索模型文件夹子目录",

        "api_hf_enable": "高清修复",
        "api_hf_scale": "放大倍率",
        "api_hf_denoise": "降噪强度",
        "api_hf_upscaler_selected": "高清修复模型",
        "api_hf_colortransfer": "色彩传递",
        "api_hf_incorrect_upscaler": "选择了错误的高清模型，使用默认 {}",
        "api_hf_random_seed":"高修随机种子(ComfyUI)",
        "api_hf_steps":"高修步数",
        
        "api_refiner_enable":"切换降噪 Refiner",
        "api_refiner_model":"切换降噪模型",
        "api_refiner_ratio":"比例",
        "api_refiner_add_noise":"切换降噪添加噪点(ComfyUI)",
        
        "run_button": "单图生成",
        "run_random_button": "批量（随机）",
        "run_same_button": "批量（上次）",
        "run_skip_button": "跳过后续",
        "run_cancel_button": "取消生成",
        "save_settings_button": "保存设置",
        "load_settings_button": "载入设置",
        
        "gr_error_creating_image":"错误：生成图片返回故障信息：\n[color=red]{0}[/color]\n请检查[color=DodgerBlue]{1}[/color]控制台输出的日志。",        
        "ai_system_prompt": "你是一个Stable Diffusion提示词编写者，按照以下指南生成提示词：\n1.禁止关键词： 不得使用任何性别相关词，如“man”、“woman”、“boy”、“girl”、“person”或类似词。\n2.格式： 提供8到16个关键词，用逗号分隔，保持简洁。\n3.内容重点： 仅关注图像的可视元素，避免抽象概念、艺术评论或意图描述。\n4.关键词类别： 确保提示词涵盖以下类别：\n    - 主题或风格 (e.g., cyberpunk, fantasy, wasteland)\n    - 地点或场景 (e.g., back alley, forest, street)\n    - 可视元素或氛围 (e.g., neon lights, fog, ruined)\n    - 镜头视角或构图 (e.g., front view, side view, close-up)\n    - 动作姿势或表情情绪 (e.g., standing, jumping, smirk, calm)\n    - 环境细节 (e.g., graffiti, trees)\n    - 时间或光线 (e.g., sunny day, night, golden hour)\n    - 额外效果 (e.g., depth of field, blurry background)\n5.创意与连贯性： 关键词选择需多样且富有创意，形成一个生动连贯的场景。\n6.用户输入： 将用户查询中的关键词逐字纳入，适当融入提示词。\n7.强调处理： 若用户强调某方面，可增加该类别关键词（最多6个），但总数保持在8到16个。\n8.角色描述： 可描述动作和表情，但不得提及角色特征（如性别、年龄）。允许使用暗示角色的词（如warrior），只要不涉及禁止词。\n9.输出： 仅以单行逗号分隔的关键词形式且必须以英文回答，不要加入关键词以外的任何回复。\n10.输出示例：nature style, eating, forest, meadow, sunlight, vibrant colors, close-up, detailed, serene, peaceful, green foliage, wild berries, natural textures, soft focus, shallow depth of field, tranquil atmosphere\nPrompt for the following theme:",
        
        "overlay_title": "后端正在生成……",
        "overlay_te": "经过时间：",
        "overlay_sec": "秒",

        "generate_ai": "等待AI返回题词……",
        "generate_start": "正在生成{0}/{1}……",
        
        "lora_info": "LoRA信息：",
        "lora_trigger_words": "触发词（热度前10）：",
        "lora_metadata": "元数据：",
        "lora_no_metadata": "文件读取错误或元数据被清除",
        "lora_model_strength": "Model强度",
        "lora_clip_strength": "CLIP强度",
        "lora_enable_title": "使用方法：开启ALL,基础Base,高修HiFix,关闭OFF",

        "right_menu_copy_image": "复制图像",
        "right_menu_copy_image_metadata": "复制图像元数据",
        "right_menu_clear_gallery": "清空画廊",
        "right_menu_test_ai_generate": "测试AI题词",
        "right_menu_send_lora_to_slot": "将LoRA读入插槽",

        "save_settings_title": "保存配置文件\n请输入要保存的文件名称：",
        "save_settings_success": "配置文件 {0} 保存成功",
        "save_settings_failed": "配置文件 {0} 保存失败",
        
        "setup_yes": "是",
        "setup_no": "否",
        "setup_ok": "确定",
        "setup_cancel": "取消",
        "setup_greet_message": "你好！在本程序第一次启动或找不到settings.json文件时，会自动运行向导程序，请按照说明进行初始化设定。",
        "setup_webui_comfyui_select": "请选择你将要使用的后端类型",
        "setup_model_folder": "请设置您的模型文件safetensors所在目录，建议从文件夹地址栏复制",
        "setup_webui_comfyui_api_addr": "请输入后端{0}的访问地址，你可以从浏览器里复制IP地址与端口",        
        "setup_model_filter": "请选择是否要开启模型白名单",
        "setup_model_filter_keyword": "请设置过滤器白名单关键字\n如果需要多个关键字，请用半角逗号隔开“,”",
        "setup_search_modelinsubfolder": "是否搜索模型文件夹子目录下的模型文件",
        
        "setup_remote_ai_interface": "设置AI语言模型接口（关闭 None,远程 Remote,本地 Local）",
        "setup_remote_ai_addr": "请输入远程语言模型API地址",
        "setup_remote_ai_model": "请输入远程语言模型名称",
        "setup_remote_ai_api_key": "请输入你的远程语言模型API密钥",
        "setup_local_ai_addr": "请输入你的本地语言模型API地址",

        "setup_done": "初始化设置完成，相关配置已经存储为 settings.json\n如果你使用ComfyUI，请在设置中开启Dev Mode\n如果你使用WebUI，请修改webui-user.bat，修改COMMANDLINE_ARGS= --api",        
        "setup_skip_wizard": "是否要跳过后续设置？"        
    }    
  }